Diana Griffing UX DESIGNER + DEVELOPER

dianalaine.us diana.griffing@gmail.com (406) 599-5740

Full Stack UX Designer from Montana with a passion for Education Technology, Social Justice, and cats.

Searching for UX Research, UX Design, or Web Development opportunities in Seattle, starting Summer / Fall 2017.

SKILLS

Research

User Research **Usability Testing** Survey Design Personas

Content Analysis

Programming

Java Python JavaScript TypeScript | HTML & CSS

Design

Information Architecture Content Strategy UX / UI Design Rapid Prototyping Wireframing

Tools

Photoshop InDesign Illustrator Lucidchart Sketch

WORK EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Reseacher University of Washington - Digital Youth Lab Dec 2015 - June 2017

Planned and led extracurricular science activities for South Seattle middle school students, using new EdTech software; assisted in extensive user testing for Science Everywhere's user interface; collected and analyzed user data; and wrote and edited research papers.

Beta Test Consultant devicebook, Bellevue

Sep 2016 - June 2017

Created and presided over a student organization to explore, learn, and design with Internet Of Things technologies, simultaneously testing a new application developed by devicebook aimed at giving tech and non-tech individuals the opportunity to learn programming skills.

Computer Science Instructor iD Tech Camp, Seattle

June 2016 - Sep 2016

Developed individual lesson plans; taught Java, python, JavaScript, game design, photoshop, photography to pre-teens and teens; assured all students had a project they were proud of at the end of the week.

Nanny Seattle

June 2014 - Sep 2015

Scheduled & planned age appropriate activities that promote physical, emotional, social, and cognitive growth; provided a safe, loving, and engaging environment; maintain strong relationship with the family for years after.

Testing Intern Quantum Design, San Diego

June 2013 - Sep 2013

Tested improvements to the VersaLab software and firmware for its summer release, calculated specifications for its new features; maintained defect tracking library.

EDUCATION

University of Washington BS in Informatics, Human-Computer Interaction Minor in Education Learning & Society Graduate 2017